Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on the Communist Party of the United States of America PE.031
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Presses and Publishing Houses, 1920-1998; 5.5 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons and 3 manuscript boxes
  - International Publishers: Pamphlets: Political Education Series, 1935-1936 (Box 8)
  - International Publishers: Pamphlets: Religion, 1932-1946 (Box 8)
  - International Publishers: Pamphlets: Stalin, Joseph I, 1929-1972 (Box 8)
  - International Publishers: Pamphlets: Stalin, Joseph II, 1929-1972 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Catalog, 1954 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: How to Make Leaflets, 1960 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets I, 1940-1949 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets II, 1940-1949 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets III, 1940-1949 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets IV, 1940-1949 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets I, 1950-1959 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets II, 1950-1959 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets I, 1960-1969, undated (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets II, 1960-1969, undated (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Africa, 1963 (Box 8)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: African-Americans/Race I, 1949-1963 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: African-Americans/Race II, 1949-1963 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Aptheker, Herbert, 1949-1960 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: China, 1945-1960 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Cuba, 1959-1961 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Dennis, Eugene, 1945-1949 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Draft Resolutions for National Conventions, 1956-1957 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Elections, 1946-1964 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley, 1949-1961 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Foster, William Z., 1945-1949 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Hall, Gus, 1951-1963 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Israel, 1953-1956 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Jewish Question/Anti-Semitism, 1947-1953 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Labor I, 1940-1969 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Labor II, 1940-1969 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Program of the Communist Party, 1954 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Soviet Union/Russia I, 1940-1969 (Box 9)
  - New Century Publishers: Pamphlets: Soviet Union/Russia II, 1940-1969 (Box 9)
  - New Outlook Publishers: Pamphlets I, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
  - New Outlook Publishers: Pamphlets II, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
  - New Outlook Publishers: Pamphlets III, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
  - New Outlook Publishers: Pamphlets I, 1970-1980, undated (Box 9)
  - New Outlook Publishers: Pamphlets II, 1970-1980, undated (Box 9)
  - New Outlook Publishers: Pamphlets III, 1970-1980, undated (Box 9)
  - New Outlook Publishers: Pamphlets, 1981-1987 (Box 9)
  - People's Daily World, 1988, undated (Box 10, Box 16, Folder 15)
  - People's Weekly World I, 1989-, undated (Box 10)
  - People's Weekly World II, 1989-, undated (Box 10)
  - People's World, 1941, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - Political Affairs I, 1947- (Box 10)
  - Political Affairs II, 1947- (Box 10)
  - Worker (New York, NY), 1949-1968, undated (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Catalogs, 1937-1943 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets, 1920-1929 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets I, 1930-1939 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets II, 1930-1939 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets III, 1930-1939 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets IV, 1930-1939 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets V, 1930-1939 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets VI, 1930-1939 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets I, 1940-1949 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets II, 1940-1949 (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets I, undated (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets II, undated (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets III, undated (Box 10)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Biographies, 1932-1940, undated (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Biography Series, undated (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Bittelman, Alexander, 1936-1943 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Browder, Earl I, 1935-1944 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Browder, Earl II, 1935-1944 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Browder, Earl III, 1935-1944 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Browder, Earl IV, 1935-1944 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Davis, Ben Jr., 1936-1943 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Executive Committee of the Communist International (ECCI) Plenum I, 1932 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Executive Committee of the Communist International (ECCI) Plenum II, 1932-1939 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Elections/Campaigns, 1940-1944 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Farmers, 1931-1943 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Ford, James, 1935-1942, undated (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Foster, William Z. I, 1930-1942 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Foster, William Z. II, 1930-1942 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Labor/Strikes/Trade Unions, 1931-1941 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Magil, A.B., 1935-1939 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Marty, Andre', 1937-1941 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Minor, Robert, 1936-1943 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Molotov, V.M., 1931, undated (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Nemo, 1934, undated (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Stalin, Joseph, 1929-1943 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Women, 1933-1945 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: World Congress of the Communist International Reports I, 1934-1936 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: World Congress of the Communist International Reports II, 1934-1936 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Young Communist International, 1935-1936 (Box 11)
  - Workers Library Publishers: Pamphlets: Young Communist International: Plenum Executive Committee Speeches, 1932 (Box 11)
- Series V: Oversize, 1932-1949; .75 Linear Feet in 1 oversize box and 2 shared oversize boxes
  - Constitution and By-Laws (1 item), 1938 (Box Shared Tamiment MSXOS002)
  - Certificates (3 items), 1935-1991 (Box Shared Tamiment MSXOS003)
  - Daily Worker (1 item), undated (Box 12)
  - Fliers and Brochures (3 items), undated (Box 12)
  - Massachusetts (5 items), 1938-1943 (Box 12)
  - New York City (4 items), 1937, undated (Box 12)
  - New York State (9 items), 1938-1948, undated (Box 12)
  - New York State: Election Campaign Committee (1 item), 1942 (Box 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings (1 item): Communist Front Organizations, 1949 (Box Shared Tamiment MSXOS002)
  - Pamphlets (2 items), undated (Box 12)
  - Poster Board on Federal Theatre (1 item), undated (Box Shared Tamiment MSXOS003)
  - Red Press Certificate (1 item), 1934 (Box 12)
  - Tecla Artwork, 1968-1970s (Box 12)
  - Waterfront Section (3 items), 1932, undated (Box 12)
  - Young Communist League: National Educational Department (1 item), circa 1943 (Box 12)